
    let september_2022 = [
        {
            question:'International Day of the Victims of Enforced Disappearances is being celebrated on which date?',
            op1:'August 3',
            op2:'August 30',
            op3:'August 28',
            op4:'August 20',
            answer: 'Answer Option B',
            exp:'International Day of the Victims of Enforced Disappearances is celebrated globally on the 30th of August every year by United Nations.'
        },
        {
            question:'India and which country has decided to set up a task force to prepare a five-year roadmap to boost bilateral defence cooperation?',
            op1:'Oman',
            op2:'Tanzania',
            op3:'Singapore',
            op4:'Bangladesh',
            answer: 'Answer: Option B ',
            exp:'India and Tanzania have decided to set up a task force to prepare a five-year roadmap to boost bilateral defence cooperation.',   
        },
        {
            question:'Which country has for the first time referred to what it called "the militarization of the Taiwan Strait", marking a rare instance?',
            op1:'Pakistan',
            op2:'Russia',
            op3:'Bangladesh',
            op4:'India',
            answer: 'Answer: Option D',
            exp:'India has for the first time referred to what it called "the militarization of the Taiwan Strait", marking a rare instance of New Delhi appearing to comment on Chinas actions towards Taiwan.',   
        },
        {
            question:'Denmarks Viktor Axelsen has clinched his second BWF World Championships men singles title in which city?',
            op1:'Berlin',
            op2:'Tokyo',
            op3:'Paris',
            op4:'Sofia',
            answer: 'Answer: Option B',
            exp:'Denmarks Viktor Axelsen has clinched his second BWF World Championships mens singles title after beating Kunlavut Vitidsarn from Thailand in Tokyo',   
        },
        {
            question:'Who has been appointed in Mercedes-Benz India as MD & CEO from January 2023?',
            op1:'Raju Tripathi',
            op2:'Sandeep Bakshi',
            op3:'Vivek Singh',
            op4:'Santosh Iyer',
            answer: 'Answer: Option D',
            exp:'German luxury carmaker Mercedes-Benz has named Santosh Iyer as the Managing Director & CEO of the Indian operations with effect from January 1, 2023.',   
        }
    ]



    
const banking = [
    {
        question: 'E-commerce major Flipkart has partnered with which of the following banks to launch the Super Elite Credit Card in November 2022?',
        op1: 'ICICI Bank',
        op2: 'HDFC Bank',
        op3: 'Axis Bank',
        op4: 'Federal Bank',
        answer: 'Answer: Option C',
        exp: 'In a bid to scale Flipkarts SuperCoins reward program, the e-commerce major and Axis Bank have partnered to launch Super Elite Credit Card',
    },
    {
        question: 'According to the data revealed by 1 Lattice (previously PNG), which of the following banks dominated the credit cards market in October 2022, with a 21% share?',
        op1: 'Axis Bank',
        o21: 'State Bank of India',
        op3: 'Indian Bank',
        op4: 'HDFC Bank',
        answer: 'Answer: Option D',
        exp: 'In the credit cards market, India s largest private sector bank, HDFC bank led the share with a whopping 21 per cent. The lead was followed by SBI Card (19%), ICICI Bank (17%), and Axis Bank (11%)',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which bank has partnered with the National E-Governance Services Ltd to launch an electronic bank guarantee?',
        op1: 'SBI',
        op2: 'Canara Bank',
        op3: 'BOI',
        op4: 'HDFC Bank',
        answer: 'Answer: Option B',
        exp: 'On its 117th Founder s day, Canara Bank launched an Electronic Bank Guarantee (e-BG) in partnership with National E-Governance Services Limited (NeSL).',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following bank has opened its first mid-corporate Branch in Kerala at Kochi?',
        op1: 'State bank of India',
        op2: 'Union Bank of India',
        op3: 'Bank of Baroda',
        op4: 'Punjab National Bank',
        answer: 'Answer: Option C',
        exp: 'Bank of Baroda has opened its first mid-corporate Branch in Kerala at Kochi.',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which bank has launched a face authentication-based savings bank account opening for customers?',
        op1: 'FINO Payments Bank',
        op2: 'Airtel Payments Bank',
        op3: 'Paytm Payments Bank',
        op4: 'India Post Payments Bank',
        answer: 'Answer Option B',
        exp: 'Airtel Payments Bank has launched a face authentication-based savings bank account opening for customers.',
    }
]

